// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who was the CLO that just passed out from A2 2022 set?",
    answer: "Momosani Sadiq",
    options: [
      "Mrs Olubodun Kikelomo",
      "Momosani Sadiq",
      "Eniola Kolapo",
      "Edward Cynthia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who is the (LGI 2) of Ekiti South West?",
    answer: "Mr Omotade O.B",
    options: [
      "Mr Kelvin Luper",
      "Mrs Olobodun Kikelomo",
      "Mr Omotade O.B",
      "Mr Alonge O."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who was the General C.D.S coordinator of Ekiti South West that just passed out from A2 2022 set?",
    answer: "Eniola kolapo",
    options: [
      "Sunday Pius",
      "Nweke Scholastica",
      "Momosani Sadiq",
      "Eniola kolapo"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is the LGI of Ekiti South West?",
    answer: "Mrs Olobodun Kikelomo",
    options: [
      "Mr Kelvin Luper",
      "Mr Alonge O.",
      "Mrs Olobodun Kikelomo",
      "Mr Omotade O.B"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What day does the monthly biometric clearance take place?",
    answer: "First Thurday of every month",
    options: [
      "Last Friday of every month",
      "First Thurday of every month",
      "First Igbara-odo market day of every month",
      "Anyday the LGI feels like calling us"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the full meaning of C.D.S?",
    answer: "Community Development Service",
    options: [
      "Community Development Scheme",
      "Compound Development Scheme",
      "Community Development Service",
      "Community Deterioration Scheme"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many Batches of Corpers does the NYSC Scheme inaugurate in a year?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "5",
      "2",
      "3",
      "1"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is the current D.G of NYSC?",
    answer: "Brig. Gen. Yushau Dogara",
    options: [
      "Brig. Gen. Shuaibu Ibrahim",
      "Gen. M.K Fadah",
      "Brig. Gen. Yushau Dogara",
      "Gen. Chikezie Mary Nnenna"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is the State cordinator of NYSC in Ekiti State?",
    answer: "Mrs Chikezie Mary Nnenna",
    options: [
      "Mr Iniabere Victor",
      "Mrs Chikezie Mary Nnenna",
      "Major Abel Agbo",
      "Mr Tosin Afolabi"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the duration of the NYSC scheme?",
    answer: "1 year",
    options: [
      "6 months",
      "2 years",
      "8 months",
      "1 year"
    ]
  },
];